Let's move! Let's go!
我們行動! 出發!
Get those VA's on!
打開VA膠管
Pull it two and a half, let's get ready to roll.
拉出兩圈半 準備好出發
Davis,get those utilities turned off.
Davis 把那些東西給關掉
Quickly! Move it!
快點! 動起來!
I'm on it,sir!
行動了 長官!
We're in front! You take the back!
我們從前門進! 你們從後門!
Scotty,you're with me! Let's move!
Scotty 你跟著我! 行動!
Fire Department!
消防局!
Let's go.
我們走
You two spread out.
你們兩分開行動
Clear the bedrooms, I'll take the kitchen.
去看看臥室 我管廚房
We'll cover this side here.
這邊我們去搞定
All right! I'm goin' right!
好的! 我去右邊的房間!
Every damn time.
該死的 每次都這樣
False alarm,fellas!
假警報 夥計們!
Just another overcooked bird.
只是另一隻煮過頭的鳥
Or something.
或者別的什麼
Tough to tell after six hours in the...
在烤箱了呆了6個小時後很難...
...oven.
...分清
"NCIS" Season 04 Episode 20
《海軍罪案調查處》 第四季 第20集
Double Americano for Thom.
給Thom的特濃美式咖啡
Aren't you Thom?
你不是Thom嗎?
Yes.
是啊
Thank you. Sorry.
謝謝 對不起
Must need that badly. Don't even recognize your own name.
一定非常需要咖啡 甚至都不知道在叫你
Medium mocha coming up.
中杯摩卡咖啡就來
It's,uh... my other name.
那是 嗯...我另一個名字
Two names,huh?
兩個名字 對不對?
Well,two jobs.
兩份工作
It's Thom when I'm writing.
我寫作的時候叫Thom
Not that I've actually written anything in weeks.
已經好幾個星期沒寫什麼東西了
Writer's block?
寫作遭遇瓶頸?
Creative stifling.
創造力貧乏
I am crumbling under the pressure of expectations.
期望給我造成壓力 我快崩潰了
Oh,you're Thom E. Gemcity.
噢 你是Thom E. Gemcity
Your photo's on the back cover.
你的照片在封底
I-I loved Deep Six.
我愛深顫
Thanks...
謝謝...
Landon. Thank you.
Landon 謝謝
Can't wait to see what happens next.
等不及下面的情節發展了
You and me both.
我們都一樣
Two weeks until my deadline,
還有2個星期就是最後期限了
I'm stuck here in Chapter Seven.
我在第七章這陷入僵局了
Well,could be worse.
可能更糟
How's that?
怎麼個糟法?
Could be Chapter Six.
可能是第六章
Okay,we got a half-caf percent latte
半咖啡因拿鐵好了
and a medium double decaf...
還有一份中杯的雙份脫咖啡因咖啡...
McGee.
McGee
Yeah.
是
The other job.
另一份工作
Good luck.
好運
Ferris Bueller's Day Off--
春天不是讀書天
John Hughes masterpiece.
John Hughes的傑作
Now,there's a guy who didn't have time for writer's block,probie.
他就是那個寫作不會陷入瓶頸的人 菜鳥
Sixteen Candles,
十六枝蠟燭
Uncle Buck,
巴克叔叔
The Breakfast Club.
早餐俱樂部
I do not have...
我沒有...
...I'm just stggling to fi out the most efficient way
...我只是努力想找出最有效的方法
to tell my next story.
來敘述我的下一個故事
Now,do you think Hughes writes on a computer
你覺得Hughes是用電腦寫作
or does he use an old-fashioned typewriter, like you?
還是像你一樣用台老式的打字機?
Well,I'm sure he uses a computer,Tony.
我確定他用的是電腦 Tony
Most writers do.
大部分作家都用
You ever consider converting?
你有沒有想過要改變?
I don't think that's the reason for my...
我覺得並不是那造成我的...
Were you gonna say writer's block?
你是不是要說寫作遭遇瓶頸?
I like my typewriter.
我喜歡我的打字機
But it doesn't like you.
但是它不喜歡你
It's a classic tale of unrequited love
那是一位男孩和他機器之前
between a boy and his machine.
單相思的經典橋段
You can use that if you want.
如果你想寫進書裡的話也可以
But remember you got to have a love story.
但是記住必須是愛情故事
I can see the poster already.
我已經想像出海報的樣子了
The house is leased to Petty Officer Darren Cove.
這間屋子是Darren Cove士官租的
No roommates, but according to the neighbors,
沒有室友 但是鄰居說
he's rarely alone.
他很少一個人呆著
I can tell.
可以看得出來
Got a fridge full of beer.
這有一冰箱的啤酒
No hard alcohol.
沒有烈性酒飲料
Except for this.
除了這個
If smells could kill,
這個味道可以熏死人
I thinkwe just found our murder weapon.
我想我們剛剛找到了謀殺兇器
I'm more concernedwith where they came from.
我更關心它們從哪而來
Neighbors said this s a notorious party house.
鄰居們說這是間聲名狼藉的派對屋
Maybe someone brought in the mixers.
也許有人帶來了這些調酒飲料
Then they left with them,too.
然後他們就加進了酒裡
Seems like a lot of effort for a couple of drinks.
看起來兌這兩杯酒下了很多功夫啊
Wasted effort.
無用功
The blood search at the Ping-Pong table.
在乒乓桌上尋找血跡
Beer-pong.
啤酒乒乓
This is tragic--
真是悲慘啊--
don't tell me you've never played beer-pong before,probie.
別告訴我你從來沒玩過啤酒乒乓 菜鳥
What did you do at MIT?
你在麻省理工裡都做些什麼?
Studied.
學習
That figures.
想像得出
Well,beer-pong is a drinking game,
啤酒乒乓是種飲酒遊戲
the object of which is to take the Ping-Pong ball,
遊戲的一方拿著乒乓球
and try and get it into the other team's cups.
想辦法把它扔進對手的杯子裡
Show me how it's done.
向我演示一下怎麼玩
This is a crime scene, not a frat house.
這是犯罪現場 不是兄弟會聯誼屋
You hearing voices,probie?
你聽到什麼聲音了 菜鳥?
Figured you saw Gibbs coming.
還以為你看到Gibbs來了呢
I just don't think this is the time or the place to
我只是認為現在不是展現啤酒乒乓技藝的
uh,showcase my beer-pong skills.
時間或者場所
What?
什麼?
Seems out of character.
似乎和你性格不符啊
Yeah,yeah.
是啊 是啊
No,you may not use me to get over your writer's block.
不 你不可以用我來克服你的寫作瓶頸
McGee has writer's block?
McGee寫作遭遇瓶頸?
No,McGee does not.
不 McGee沒有
Just do what you did last time-- write about us.
就做你上次做過的事情好了-- 寫寫我們
Okay,I've told you guys a million times, the book is not about you.
我告訴過你們無數次了 那本書寫的不是你們
No,of course not-- it's about Special Agent Tommy.
當然不是了 寫的只是Tommy探員
And Officer Lisa.
還有Lisa官員
DiNozzo!
And L.J. Tibbs.
還有L.J. Tibbs
Get this.
看這個
Looks like McGee wasn't the only writer here today.
看起來McGee不是今天在這唯一的作家
Bag it.
把它打包
Petty Officer Cove joined the Navy three years ago,
Cove士官3年前加入海軍的
right out of high school.
高中一畢業就參軍了
His CO says he's a little immature, but basically a good kid.
他的長官說他有點點的不成熟 但基本上還是個好孩子
Good kid with a criminal record.
有犯罪記錄的好孩子
Since enlisting,he's been arrested twice, both misdemeanors.
自從參軍以來 他已經被捕2次了 都是輕罪
Public intox in '04, and a noise ordinance violation last July.
在04年破壞公物還有去年7月違反噪音條例
"Works to live,and lives to party.」
"工作是為了生活 生活是為了派對」
His,uh...
他的 唔...
CO's words.
長官說的
Guys in his command call him Darren "Diddy" Cove.
他手下的士兵都叫他Darren "Diddy" Cove
Why?
為什麼?
Uh,it's a reference to Sean Diddy Combs.
這個和Sean Diddy Combs有聯繫
The Puff Man,P Diddy.
那個Puff Man;P Diddy(吹牛老爹)
Rap impresario.
唱Rap的
Went out with J-Lo.
和J-Lo出去約會的
Petty Officer Cove was on duty yesterday.
Cove軍士昨天當班
Left the base at 1800,hasn't been seen since.
在18:00離開基地 那之後就沒人見過他了
And neither has his blue Ford Ranger.
他的藍色福特Ranger也不見蹤影
Should be in his garage,but it's not.
應該在他的車庫裡 但是不在
Which means his attacker took it.
那就是說攻擊他的人弄走了
Or Petty Officer Cove went for a drive.
或者Cove軍士開出去了
With that amount of blood loss, it's doubtful he was conscious.
失了那麼多血還開車 很懷疑他是不是還有意識
If it was all his blood.
如果那都是他的血的話
Well,Abby'll tell us,because Cove's blood sample is in his medical records.
Abby會告訴我們的 因為Cove的 血液樣本在他的醫療記錄裡有
I'm gonna go check the BOLO, see if he's got a hit on the pickup.
我要去查下警方通告 看看有沒有吻合的車輛
That's not necessary,McGee.
沒這必要 McGee
Norfolk Police just found it abandoned along Highway 5.
諾福克警方剛剛找到它 被丟棄在高速公路旁
I've noticed oversized dice like these in numerous vehicles.
我在很多車裡 都見過這種特大型的骰子
Do they serve a purpose?
他們掛上去有什麼目的的吧?
Hello?
喂?
- Tony? - What?
- Tony? - 什麼?
Do they serve a purpose?
他們掛上去有什麼目的的吧?
Fuzzy dice-- pretty good redneck indicator.
長毛絨骰子 很明顯他是鄉下人
Other than that,no, they don't serve a purpose.
除那之外 沒了 它們沒什麼目的性的
Got a lot more blood back here,boss.
車後面找到更多的血跡 頭
Think this was used to cover the body?
這個應該是裹屍體用的?
Yeah. Or bodies.
是的 或者幾具屍體
Yeah,Abs-- I'm listening.
是 Abs 我在聽
McGee,you look like you've seen a goat.
McGee 你看上去像看到了"色鬼"
Huh? Oh. Ghost.
啊? 噢 幽靈
"Seen a ghost.」
"看見了幽靈"
Yeah.
是的
Do you know what deja vu is?
你知道"似曾相識"的感覺嗎?
Bien sur.
當然
My French is better than my English.
我的法語要比我的英語要好
Right.
對
So...
那麼...
What?
什麼?
The deja vu.
似曾相識
I can't place it.
我找不到這感覺了
By any chance, did you start dating someone,McGee?
有沒可能你開始約會了 McGee?
Dating?
約會?
Please,I spend every spare minute I have writing.
拜託 我把業餘時間都花在寫作上了
Hang on a second.
等一下
McGee.
McGee
Get this towed back to lockup.
把這個拖回局裡
Yeah,go on,Abs.
好了 繼續 Abs
Abby's got something.
Abby發現了些什麼
Watch out!
看呀!
It's Halloween at Coyote Ugly, Piper Perabo.
這是在Coyote Ugly(電影名 講述紐約最熱門的酒吧)的萬聖節前夕 Piper Perabo
Oh,if you like that one, you're gonna love this.
噢 如果你喜歡那個 那麼你也會喜歡這個的
It's a,uh,it's a Sciuto original.
這是Sciuto(Abby)原創的
I like to call it "Bottoms Up.」
我喜歡叫它"底朝天"
I had no idea you were a bartender,Abby.
我不知道你還做過酒吧招待 Abby
Well,my Uncle Teddy used to own a bar on Canal Street,
我的叔叔Teddy以前在Canal街有間酒吧
and I used to bartend there on the weekends.
我經常在週末在那當侍應
The case,Abby?
案子 Abby?
But,Gibbs,you haven't even seen my famous Fire Bomb.
但是 Gibbs 你還沒欣賞過 我著名的燃燒彈呢
It can wait.
那不急
So,uh,I tested the blood that was in Petty Officer Cove's house.
我檢測了在Cove軍士房子裡的血跡
Most of it was his, but one sample did not match.
大部分是他的 但是有個樣本不吻合
It could've been from a prior accident or an altercation at one of his parties.
可能是之前的某個派對上 發生的意外或者口角時留下的
Or it could be the killer's.
也可能是兇手的
I also ran...
我還查了...
the prints from our mystery cocktails.
神秘的雞尾酒杯上的指紋
One half of our drinking duo was definitely Petty Officer Cove.
這兩杯飲料上一半指紋是Cove士官的
The other half?
另外一半呢?
Well,it's a work in progress,Gibbs.
還在查 Gibbs
Tell me you have more than this,Abby.
告訴我你不止查到這些 Abby
Have I ever let you down?
我有讓你失望過嗎?
Don't answer that.
別回答
Um,I'm using my mass spectrometer to break down
我用質譜儀分解了
the molecular structure of the cocktails in question.
可疑雞尾酒中的分子結構
Guessing that's where all these come in.
我猜就是變成這些東西的吧
Well,you guessed correctly.
猜測正確
I think I've made over 100 delightful beverages trying to find...
我想我製成超過100種好喝的飲料 想要找出...
the match.
符合這種的
The weird thing is, this baby isn't in any bartending guide anywhere.
奇怪的是 這個寶貝任何 任何酒吧侍應指南中都找不到
It's made out of Jagermeister...
它的配方是野格酒...
Cherry soda,vanilla vodka, lemon juice and a splash of Tabasco.
櫻桃蘇打 香草味伏特加 檸檬汁 再加一滴塔巴斯哥辣醬油
It's called a "Hairy Hangover.」
叫做"危險宿醉"
And you came to know this how,McGee?
你怎麼會知道的 McGee?
I created it.
我創造的
******
我們失蹤的士官是我下本書的角色
Cameron Meyer is a good old boy from Northern Virginia.
Cameron Meyer是從南佛吉尼亞 一個很好的大男孩
"He was born with not much, raised with even less."
"他出生的時候一貧如洗 成長過程中被賦予的更少得可憐"
All he wants out of life is a good girl and a great truck.
他只渴望生命中有個好姑娘和輛好車
"As of yesterday,he's halfway there."
"而在昨天 他已經成功一半了"
He dropped his life savings on a blue Ford Ranger.」
"他用他一生的積蓄 買了輛藍色的福特越野車"
That's it?
就這些?
Tony,it's all here.
Tony 就這麼多了
The fuzzy dice,the cinnamon rolls, red track jacket.
長毛絨骰子 肉桂卷 紅色的田徑夾克
Petty Officer Cove is Cameron Meyer.
Cove軍士就是Cameron Meyer.
Uh,but how is that possible,McGee?
但那怎麼可能呢 McGee?
My writing isn't entirely fiction. Okay?
我寫的東西並不是完全虛構的 知道嗎?
My stories are,
我的故事是虛構的
but sometimes I base my characters on people I...
但有時人物的原型是那些...
Work with.
一起工作的
See.
看見的
People I see.
我看見的人
You've seen Petty Officer Cove before?
你以前見過Cove士官?
Every morning at my coffee shop.
每天早上在我喝咖啡的店裡
But how come you didn't recognize his photograph?
但你怎麼會沒認出他的照片呢?
He only uses the drive-through.
他只使用"得來速"服務
To me,he's just the large coffee with a cinnamon roll guy in the blue pickup.
對我來說 他只是個坐在藍色車裡 買大杯咖啡和肉桂卷的人
I never saw his face.
我從沒見過他長什麼樣
Whoa,whoa,wait-wait a minute.
哇 哇 等 等一下
Back up.
倒回去
Your coffee shop has a drive-through?
你喝咖啡的店有"得來速"窗口?
That's...That's not important.
那...那不重要
Just because you based your character on a person who is missing,
就因為你人物的原型失蹤了
does not necessarily mean the two of them are related,McGee.
並不代表這兩者有聯繫啊 McGee
Yeah,it does.
有聯繫
You created the drink.
你創造了那款飲料
Made it up about a month ago.
大約一個月前想出來的
How did two glasses of it get from your head
其中的兩杯怎麼從你的腦袋瓜裡出來
to inside Petty Officer Cove's house?
跑到Cove軍士的房子裡去的?
Someone's read your book.
有人讀過你的書
Your papers under lock and key?
你的文章有妥善保管吧?
Well,I sent my publisher a copy a couple weeks ago,
我幾周前給我的發行人寄了個副本
but,you know,I'm sure she...
但是 我肯定她...
Address.
地址
boss,there's more.
頭 還有些別的事
Uh,after Deep Six hit the stores,
在深顫上市之後
my publishing firm received a ton of e-mails addressed to Thom E. Gemcity.
我的出版公司收到了很多郵件 是寄給Thom E. Gemcity的
Tons?
很多?
Most of them are autograph requests or feedback on the novel,
大部分是要親筆簽名或者是對小說的反饋
but in the last couple weeks,
但在最近幾周
my publisher says that we've gotten some really weird letters,
我的發行人說收到些很奇怪的信
borderline obsessive.
到了著魔的邊緣
I didn't say anything because I assumed they were harmless.
我沒說什麼因為我覺得他們沒什麼危險
DiNozzo,with me.
DiNozzo 跟我走
McGee,you stay here with Ziva.
McGee 你跟Ziva呆在這
Start going through your book.
把你的書細讀一遍
What exactly am I looking for?
我到底要找什麼?
Answers,McGee.
答案 McGee
Miss Crawshaw will be with you shortly.
Crawshaw小姐很快就來見你們
Oh,you got to be kidding me.
這一定是在開玩笑吧
Is there anything else I can get you while you wait?
你們等候時需要些什麼嗎?
Yeah,a barf bag.
是的 嘔吐袋
I'm sorry.
對不起
Todd,black tea,lemon,crab salad,arugula.
Todd 紅茶 檸檬 蟹肉沙拉 芝麻菜
You're Timothy's people.
你們是Timothy的同事
A few weeks ago, he sent you a draft of his next book?
幾周前他寄給你他下本書的草稿?
Partial. It wasn't finished yet.
部分的 還沒完成呢
Yeah,it still isn't,is it?
是啊 還沒完成呢 對嗎?
How many of your people here have read the book?
你們這裡多少人讀過這本書了?
Zero.
No one in my agency has access to advance material
我這裡沒人能讀到還未出版的原作
without the writer's consent.
除非經過作者同意
Except you.
除了你
Writers are notoriously insecure.
作者們是非常不可靠的
Soft,even.
甚至是軟弱
Well,that doesn't sound like our little Timmy McGee now,does it?
聽上去不像是我們的小Timmy McGee 對吧?
Whether they ask for it or not,
不管他們是不是要求
I provide coddling,prodding,protection.
我提供周到的 監督型的保護
Anything it takes to keep those elusive muses singing.
想盡一切辦法讓那些難以捉摸的 "繆斯"歌唱(指保持靈感)
Agent...?
請問貴姓...?
Gibbs.
Gibbs
Here we go. Rock Hollow:
找到了 空谷
The Continuing Adventures of L.J. Tibbs.
L.J. Tibbs的冒險新歷程
How is this connected with your investigation?
這和你們的調查怎麼會有關係呢?
A person's missing.
一個人失蹤了
We believe it's related to the contents of that book.
我們相信和這本書的內容有關
Guess I just made myself your prime suspect.
我猜我剛把自己變成你們的頭號嫌疑犯
Sounds about right.
言之有理
I may be the only one in the firm who's read it, Agent Gibbs,
我應該是公司裡唯一一個 讀過小說的人 Gibbs探員
but I can guarantee you I'm not the only one in the city.
但我跟你肯定 我不是這城裡唯一一個讀過的人
McGee hasn't given the book to anyone else, Miss Crawshaw.
McGee沒有把書給其他人看過 Crawshaw小姐
Obsessed fans always find a way to get material early.
瘋狂粉絲總是會找到捷足先登的方法
They dig through trash,hack computers,
他們翻垃圾 當黑客
anything short of writing it themselves.
所有上面寫有字的東西
And believe me, Timothy has some of the craziest fans I've ever seen.
相信我 Timothy擁有些 我聞所未聞的瘋狂粉絲
Yeah,we know about the letters.
對 我們知道信的事
Yeah,there are three that stand out.
沒錯 三個粉絲站出來
Todd,bring me those three...
Todd 給我把那三封...
Gemcity letters?
Gemcity的信?
No return addresses.
沒有回郵地址
Each one's stranger than the last.
一封比一封奇怪
I bet the psychopath you're looking for is somewhere in that envelope.
我肯定你一定可以在信的某處找到那個變態
What makes you think we're looking for a psychopath?
你為什麼會覺得我們找的是個變態?
Don't you read crime novels?
你們不看犯罪小說嗎?
There are always psychopaths.
裡面總是有變態出沒
"I am sending this letter to express my gratitude
"我在此表達我內心的感激"
"for the literary gift you've given me.
"感謝你給我這份文學大禮"
"The majesty of your writing
"你文字的精妙
is far beyond anything this planet has ever seen."
前無古人後無來者"
A rave review.
高度讚譽
Rave,indeed,Jethro.
讚譽 的確 Jethro
Yeah.
對
In fact,it's quite possible that
看來 這個Michael很可能是
Michael is Timothy's greatest admirer.
Timothy的頭號崇拜者
Admirer,or stalker,Duck?
崇拜者 還是跟蹤狂 Duck?
At this point,I'd say
從這點上 我要說
he is no immediate threat to himself or anyone else.
他尚不會對自己或者他人造成威脅
At this point?
從哪點?
Well,one does not become a predatory stalker overnight,Jethro.
沒人會在一夜之間變成激進跟蹤狂的 Jethro
The mind typically goes through three stages.
這種思想一般經歷三個階段
This letter,strange as it may seem,
這封信 看上去古里古怪
is only at stage one-- the attraction stage.
僅僅是第一階段--情有獨鍾
And the other two?
那剩下兩個呢?
Well,on the surface,
從表面來看
this letter,written by Andrew,
這封信 作者是Andrew
would appear more normal,
看上去正常些
but phrases like "I breathe for your words"
但卻使用了"我呼吸著你的文字"
and "you need me,"
還有"你需要我"等句子
might suggest...
極可能顯示...
Otherwise.
事實相反
Yeah,because of that sense of desperation,
對 因為這種極度絕望的語氣
I categorized that letter as stage two-- obsession.
我把這封信歸為第二階段--陷入瘋狂
What's stage three?
第三階段是什麼?
Well,read for yourself.
你自己讀讀看
"I know you think of me often, just as I think of you.
"我知道你時刻想著我 就像我時刻想著你一樣
Please don't make me do something we'll both regret.」
不要逼我做出讓雙方都後悔的事"
Now,that letter has an aggressive, and thatening tone.
現在 這封信帶著挑釁和威脅的語氣
For that reason, it falls into the final stage--
因此 它進入了最後的階段
destruction.
摧毀
Three letters.
三封信
Three stages.
三個階段
I know what you're thinking,Jethro,
我知道你在想什麼 Jethro
but it's no coincidence.
但沒有那麼巧的事
Although the letters may appear to be very different,
雖然這些信表面上看上去很不一樣
the writing style is nearly identical in all three.
但三封的書寫風格如出一轍
The same person wrote all three.
是同一個人寫的
And judging by the postmarks,
而且從郵戳來看
the letters were written and sent over a period of several weeks.
著些信是在幾個禮拜以內寫成並寄出的
During which time,
在那段時間
the writer became increasingly delusional.
寫信人逐漸陷入妄想
Motive?
動機?
Well,I can't say for certain,
呃 我不能肯定
but I'd say the answers can be found in Timothy's new book.
但我敢說答案一定能在Timothy的新書裡找到
The writer believes that
寫信人相信
Timothy's fiction is very much real.
Timothy的小說是真實的
Tony,you about...
Tony 你快...
Done.
好了
So?
怎樣?
I'm confused.
我很困惑
This isn't a critique,okay?
不是要你評論 知道嗎?
We're trying to find something useful...
我們正在尋找有用的線索...
Confused by what?
為了什麼困惑?
The plot,the back story, pretty much everything.
情節 故事背景 幾乎全部
The whole thing doesn't make sense.
整個故事簡直不知講什麼
Ziva,what about you?
Ziva 你呢?
Well,not as confused as Tony.
呃 沒有Tony那麼困惑
Well,I haven't finished it yet.
呃 我還沒寫完
It's just a rough draft.
這只是一個粗稿
Very rough.
真的很粗
I'm sorry,McGee.
對不起 McGee
Who's the killer,anyway?
那 兇手是誰?
I don't know yet.
我還不知道
There's your problem.
這就是你的問題了
I mean,yeah,you always have to know where your story is going.
我意思是 你得一直清楚你故事的走向
That's Fiction Writing 101.
這是小說寫作101條準則
Not the way I choose to write,Tony.
那不是我選擇的寫作方式 Tony
And he wonders why he has writer's block.
而且他想知道為什麼他也有瓶頸
Can we focus on the problem here?
我們能把精力放在眼前的問題上嗎?
We've got a missing person and our only lead is my book.
有人失蹤了 唯一線索就是我的書
Well,that's not much of a lead.
這可算不上什麼唯一線索
She's right. We don't even know how the book factors in.
她說得沒錯 我們甚至不知道書的因素有多大
We do now.
現在知道了
The letters were written by the same person.
三封信都是同一個人寫的
He thinks the book is real.
他認為書裡的描寫是真實的
And believes Petty Officer Cove is a part of it.
還相信士官Cove就是其中的一部分
It means we're going to have to go everywhere he's been.
意思是我們要去所有他去過的地方
Well,we've already done that,though.
呃 我們已經去過了
His home,work,hangout spots.
他的家 工作地點 休閒場所
I'm not talking about Petty Officer Cove.
我不是說士官Cove
I'm talking about your good old boy--
我是指你的老相好
with the pickup truck.
開小型貨車那個
Cameron Meyer.
Cameron Meyer
High Side Creek, where Cameron goes to clear his head.
高邊灣 Cameron經常來這裡清理思路
Thematically, this location is very important,boss.
從主題上來說 這個地點非常重要 頭
You've been saying the same thing all morning,McGee.
你整個早上都在說這件事 McGee
Spread out.
分頭搜索
Why would Cameron come to a picnic area to think?
為什麼Cameron在一個 人家野餐的地方思考?
In his book,it's not a picnic area.
在他書裡 這裡不是野餐用的
It's his favorite fishing hole.
他最喜歡來這裡釣魚
Thank you,Ziva.
謝謝 Ziva
Don't you think it's kind of a clich?
你不覺得這有點老套嗎?
to have your character alone,
讓你的角色獨處
staring into the serene wilderness?
望著寂靜的大自然發呆?
No. If it was, I wouldn't have written it,Tony.
不 如果老套 我是不會這麼寫的 Tony
I mean,knowing Cameron, if he was bummed out,
我說 瞭解了Cameron 如果他不高興
wouldn't he just go to the Wing Shack with his buddies,
他就不能跟老友們去Wing Shack酒吧
and toss back a few brews?
喝幾杯小酒?
Or talk to a priest?
或者去跟神父傾訴?
Don't forget that he's very religious, now that his father died.
別忘了他可是個虔誠的教徒 現在他父親又死了
Good point.
說得好
No,it isn't.
不 不是這樣的
Cameron keeps his emotions bottled up.
Cameron是個壓抑情緒的人
When he's upset,he comes here.
當他難過時 他就來這
Afterwards,he always feels better.
然後 他心情就會好轉
Not always.
不一定
That's him.
是他
That's Petty Officer Cove.
這是士官Cove
Then who is this?!
那這是誰?
That's Jared Brenner.
這是Jared Brenner
That's another character from my book.
我書裡的另外一個角色
Two bodies,
兩具屍體
both with nearly identical stab wounds in the chest and abdomen.
胸部和腹部的刀傷一摸一樣
It appears that Petty Officer Cove may have put up a bit of a struggle.
這表明士官Cove曾經掙扎過一陣
Note the remnants of skin tissue and blood under the fingernails..
從指甲裡的皮膚殘留組織 和血跡可以看出來
Both men have been deceased for less than 24 hours.
兩個人的死亡時間都不超過24小時
That is not all they have in common,Ducky.
這不是他們唯一的共同點 Ducky
They're also both characters in McGeek's next book.
他們都是McGee下本書的角色
Yes. From what I hear, Timothy, in your next novel,
對 我聽說了 Timothy 在你下本小說裡
L.J. Tibbs has a love interest.
L.J. Tibbs 有一段曖昧關係
Yes.
對
I hear that it's an Army...
我聽說是個軍隊...
Ducky,I don't think we need to talk about that.
Ducky 我覺得我們不該討論這個
Army what? McGee?
軍隊的什麼? McGee?
Lieutenant.
陸軍中尉
Colonel.
Colonel
Lieutenant colonel.
Colonel中尉
You got a murder weapon,Duck?
你找到兇器了 Duck?
Yes,well,that's where things get interesting,Jethro.
對 有趣的是 Jethro
Both wounds are circular about one inch in diameter.
兩個傷口都是直徑大約一英吋的圓形
- Javelin. - Javelin.
- 標槍 - 標槍
Chapter Four.
第四章
My characters Cameron Meyer and Jared Brenner—
我書裡的Cameron Meyer和Jared Brenner...
they murder a convenience store clerk to cover up an extortion.
在搶劫中殺了一個便利店店員滅口
Javelin.
標槍
Believe it or not.
不管你信不信
That is for what they were originally intended,Anthony.
這是他們原本的意圖 Anthony
A javelin as a modern-day murder weapon.
用標槍作為一件現代時髦的兇器
I applaud your creativity,McGee.
我為你的創意叫好 McGee
Of course,well...
當然 呃...
given the circumstances...
也要視環境而...
Oh,dear.
哦 天
Now I'm gonna have to read his new book.
現在我得去讀讀他的新書了
Petty Officer Darren Cove and Adrian Corbett,
士官Darren Cove和Adrian Corbett
the inspiration behind two of McGee's characters:
McGee兩個角色的原型
Cameron Meyer and Jared Brenner.
Cameron Meyer和Jared Brenner.
Any other connection?
兩人還有其他聯繫嗎?
Not that we've found.
還沒找到
Corbett worked as a valet at Alfonso's Steakhouse.
Corbett在Alfonso牛排餐館做侍應
Your favorite.
你的最愛
That's how I got to know him.
這就是我認識他的原因
For my book,I borrowed his physical details—
在我書裡 我借用了他身體上的特徵
the nose ring, birthmark on the face and the neck.
鼻環 臉上和脖子上的胎記
What was his job?
他的工作是什麼?
Valet at a steakhouse.
牛排餐館的侍應
But I did change the name of the restaurant.
但我改掉了餐館的名字
From Alfonso's to fredo's.
從Alfonso改成Afredo
Don't need to be Sherlock Holmes to figure that one out.
不一定只有福爾摩斯才猜得到
The note from Petty Officer Cove's apartment.
從士官Cove的公寓找到的紙條
"One down,two to go.」
"死了一個 還有兩個"
Means the killer's not finished.
意思是兇手還未完成
How many more of your characters did you base on real people?
你還有多少個角色是基於現實人物的?
Hey.
嘿
How many?
多少個?
Just the team.
就是我們隊
You.
你
Tony,Ziva,everyone.
Tony Ziva 所有人
You happy,Tony?
你高興了 Tony?
I finally admitted it.
我終於承認了
I based both my novels on you guys.
我兩本小說都是以你們為原型的
That means we're all potential targets.
意思是我們都是潛在目標
Boss,I'm sorry.
頭 對不起
Ducky,Abby,Palmer-- 24-hour security detail until we find this psycho.
Ducky abby Palmar...二十四小時監控 直到我們找到那個神經病為止
27 javelins sold in the DC area in the past six months.
特區過去六個月賣出了27根標槍
21 were paid for by credit cards,
21根是用信用卡付帳的
all by track coaches and athletic directors.
買家都是田徑教練和運動員指導
at about the last six?
那剩下六個呢?
Cash transactions.
現金交易
Yeah. Gibbs.
對 Gibbs
Got them for you,Gibbs.
找到了 Gibbs
Got it,Abs. We'll be right down.
知道了 Abs 我們馬上下去
Go,go.
走 走
Not you.
你不用
Two men are dead because of me,boss.
兩個人因為我而死了 頭
You got a javelin,McGee?
你有標槍嗎 McGee?
No,but I own a typewriter.
不 但我有個打字機
It's a typewriter,not a shotgun.
那是個打字機 不是手槍
It cost two men their lives
它送掉了兩條人命
because I based my fictional book on real people.
就因為我在小說裡用了真人做原型
Then put these on.
那銬上這個
You just confessed,right?
你剛剛承認了 不是嗎?
Not exactly.
不完全是這樣
There's no mid ground,McGee.
沒有中間地帶 McGee
You either put on the cuffs or you find who's responsible.
你要不就自己銬上 要不就找出誰是兇手
How?
怎樣找?
This guy's inside your head.
這傢伙在你腦海裡
You get inside his!
你來找出他在想什麼!
Boss,it's not that simple.
頭 不是那麼簡單的
I still don't even know what my story...
我自己還不知道小說怎樣...
You figure it out,McGee!
那你就搞清楚 McGee!
You write the ending to this or the killer will!
結束這個故事的人 不是你就是兇手!
Well,McGee feels bad enough.
嗯 McGee感覺糟透了
Only makes it worse that he admitted it.
他承認只會讓情況更糟
It was no secret he was writing about us.
他寫的是我們 這已經不是秘密了
Oh,come on. It's not about us.
哦 別這樣 寫的不是我們
I mean,the whole part about Lisa and her broken heart.
我意思是 Lisa和她傷透心的那部分
The memento she keeps from her relationship that never had a chance to happen.
源於她從未有機會展開的戀情
Yeah,where's he getting that?
對 他從哪裡編出這些的
Or the scene between Lisa and Tommy
還有那些Lisa和Tommy兩人的場景
where they pour out their hearts to each other and spill their secrets?
當兩人推心置腹 互訴衷腸的時候?
When he tries to explain the profound nature of his identity crisis.
當他試圖解釋他身份危機的深刻意義
Yeah. I mean,the hidden struggle between who he is and what he's becoming.
對 我意思是 他內心深處對他身份和未來的掙扎
I don't even know what that is.
我甚至那是什麼都不知道
Yeah,totally unrealistic.
對 完全不真實
Would never happen.
從沒發生過
What do you got,Abs?
你找到什麼 Abs?
Three hours sleep.
三小時小睡
My apartment flooded last night.
我的公寓昨晚淹水了
Did you know that trying to flush voodoo dolls down the toilet is a bad idea?
你知道把巫毒娃娃從馬桶 沖掉是個很爛的主意嗎?
I do now.
我現在知道了
Where's Gibbs?
Gibbs呢?
He's chomping up McGee.
他正在狂咬McGee
Chewing.
狂罵
So a little birdie told me
小小鳥告訴我 (來自Alfred Tennyson的詩)
that  both of you have read the first half of McGee's new book.
你們兩個都讀過McGee新書的前半部了
A little birdie,huh?
小小鳥?
And don't even ask because I will not reveal my source evenf you torture me.
別問 因為就算你嚴刑逼供 我也不會告訴你我從哪裡知道的
- Ducky? - Yes!
- Ducky? - 對
All right,let's hear it.
好吧 來聽聽
Hear what?
聽什麼?
The book.
書啊
At the end of Deep Six,
在深顫 的結尾
goth forensic specialist "Amy Sutton,"
歌特風格的法醫鑒證專家"Amy Sutton"
she broke up with her boyfriend because she was digging somebody else.
她和男朋友分手了 因為她和別人在一起
Who's the somebody else?
那個別人是誰?
Oh,yeah,um...
哦 對 呃...
Yeah,that part really didn't come up yet.
對 那部分還沒真正結束
Yeah,I think he's planning on revealing it,
對 我覺得他打算揭開謎底的
uh,in,you know,the second part of the book.
你知道 在書的第二部分
You guys are so lying.
你們都是大話精
He's gay!
他是同性戀!
The somebody else!
那個別人!
I had a feeling 'cause Amy always wants what Amy cannot have.
我有這種感覺 因為Amy總是想擁有那些得不到的東西
Does she know?
她知道嗎?
Know what?
知道什麼?
Forensic specialist Amy, she fell in love with a gay guy,Gibbs.
法證專家Amy 她愛上了一個同性戀 Gibbs
That why I'm here?
我是為這個來的嗎?
No.
不是
Then Amy's on her own.
那就讓Amy一個人呆著
We'll talk later.
我們晚點再談
Um,I ran the blood samples that we pulled off the two bodies.
我檢查了兩具屍體上的血樣
Petty ficer Cove had unidentified blood on his right forearm and hand.
士官Cove右前臂和手上有不明血跡
It matched the blood from his house.
和他屋子裡的血跡相符合
Our killer's DNA.
兇手的DNA
I'm no investigator, but odds are you're right.
我不是探員 但你是對的
That's good work,Abs.
做得好 Abs
I also checked Petty Officer Cove's Ford Ranger
我也檢查了士官Cove的福特越野車
and Thom E.Gemcity's c-mail for prints.
還有Thom E.Gemcity 鴨郵件上的指紋
C-mail?
鴨郵件?
Yeah,it's like cuckoo mail.
對 就像鴨尾酒郵件
No,no,no,I just made it up.
不不不 我剛編的
Um,nothing on the truck.
呃 車上什麼都沒有
All the latent prints belong to Petty Officer Cove.
所有的指紋都是士官Cove的
But on the c-mail, there's dozens of different prints.
但是在鴨郵件有十幾個不同的指紋
Well,that makes sense 'cause paper mail gets processed
那就說得通了 因為郵件會經過很多流程
through post offices, delivery trucks,mailrooms.
郵局 郵車 收發室
Exactly.
沒錯
There's still one spot that only the sender touches.
但有一個地方是只有寄信人會觸摸到的
The back of the stamp.
郵票的背面
You pulled a print?
你提取指紋了?
Not only did I pull a print, I already got a match.
不僅僅提取了 還找到了符合對像
Todd Ryder,
Todd Ryder
arrested last year for possession of marijuana.
去年因為私藏大麻被逮捕
Looking for something,Timothy?
在找什麼 Timothy
I'm just looking.
我只是看看
Petty Officer Cove... ....
士官Cove...
wasn't just a partier.
並不是一個花天酒地的人
I called his elderly parents.
我給他的父母打了電話
Visited em every day for two hours.
每天花兩小時去看他們
This guy,Adrian Corbett,
這人名叫Adrian Corbett
he just got married.
新婚不久
Yes,I took off his wedding ring.
是的 我摘下了他的婚戒
Not quite the notorious playboy I made him out to be,huh?
跟我塑造的臭名昭著的 花花公子形象相去甚遠吧？
Appearances can be deceptive.
不能以貌取人
Every single word I wrote was wrong.
我寫下的每個字都鑄成了錯
No,every word you wrote was fiction.
不 你的字字句句都是在虛構小說
That's why they call them "characters.」
所以他們稱之為"角色"
But they're not just characters in a book.
但在書裡他們不僅僅是角色
They're real people...
他們有血有肉...
and real families.
有真正的家庭
Were.
曾經如此
I sympathize with the way you feel, Timothy......
我明白你有多難受 Timothy...
but you are not to blame for any of this.
但這一切都不能怪你
Tell them that.
跟他們說去吧
Todd!
Oh,God.
哦 我的天
Look out!
小心!
What do you call that?
你把那叫成什麼?
Running,I think.
我想是 跑
Todd!
嗨!
Where's his car?
他的車在哪兒?
Where's his car?!
他的車在哪兒?!
Employee lot around back.
後面的員工車位
Get out of the building!
快離開大樓!
They know!
他們知道了!
They're chasing me!
他們在追趕我!
You should've left the top down.
你真該把敞篷打開
Put your hands on top of your head.
把手舉過頭頂
Nice of you to join us,DiNozzo.
你能加入我們真是太好了 DiNozzo
thought I was gaining ground.
以為我要佔上風了呢
He got a very unorthodox running style.
他的跑步風格很另類
It's very effective,though.
但非常有效
Not effective enough.
還不夠有效
I didn't want to do it.
我不想這麼做
I told her it was a bad idea.
我跟她說了這是個餿主意
I actually trusted her.
我真的信任過她
There was no way you could have known,McGee.
你不可能知道的 McGee
Ziva's right,probie, it's not your fault.
Ziva說得對 菜鳥 這不能怪你
But if you even think about writing a third novel,I'll kill you.
但如果你還想寫第三部小說 我會殺了你
When Abby finds out who her character really fell in love with,
如果Abby查明她的角色跟誰傾心相愛
you will already be dead.
你也必死無疑
I have been sitting here half the night,Agent Gibbs.
我在這兒坐了半個晚上了 Gibbs探員
What am I being charged with?
我被指控犯了什麼罪?
Tampering with a federal investigation.
妨礙聯邦調查
That'sidiculous.
荒謬
I've answered every question you've asked.
所有問題我都一五一十回答了
Resisting arrest.
拒捕
I told you already,I wasn't running.
我告訴你了 我沒在逃跑
I was late for an appointment.
而是約會遲到了
And murder.
加上謀殺
You think I murdered someone?
你認為我殺人了?
Their names are Petty Officer Darren Cove and Adrian Corbett.
他們是士官Darren Cove和Adrian Corbett
Never heard of 'em.
從沒聽說過
Okay.
好吧
Well, how about Cameron Meyer and Jared Brenner?
那Cameron Meyer和Jared Brenner呢?
Have you heard of them?
聽說過他們嗎?
I think so.
我覺得是
They're characters in Tim's next book.
他們是Tim下一本書裡的角色
A book someone is killing over.
有人殺死了書裡的人
Too bad you can't find them.
真遺憾 你找不到他們
I think we have.
我認為已經找到了
You wrote the letters.
這些信是你寫的
What?! Why would I...?
什麼?!我為什麼要...?
Todd gave you up.
Todd把你供出來了
He said you told him to mail the letters back to the agency.
說你讓他把信件寄回出版社
Well,I can explain.
我可以解釋
Well,I sure hope .
我當然希望如此
I wrote the letters,
我寫這些信
but only to create a bigger buzz.
只不過是為了引起轟動
Stalkers mean more press.
跟蹤狂意味著更多發行量
More press means increased revenue.
更多發行量意味著更多的收入
You made up a stalker to sell more books?
為了增加書的銷售你捏造了一個跟蹤狂?
Yes,I did.
是的 沒錯
She's lying.
她在撒謊
If she is,she's quite good.
如果是 她的表演就太出色了
She publishes fictional novels for a living,Ziva.
她靠出版虛構小說謀生 Ziva
She knows how to tell a good story.
她知道怎麼把故事講得生動
I'm with Ziva.
我同意Ziva
This woman lives to sell books.
這女人靠售書為生
Look,it may sound unorthodox,
聽著 也許聽起來很陰險
but I do one interview about those letters
但我為一些類似信件做了次採訪
and Gemcity's book sales jump through the roof.
Gemcity的書的銷量就一路飆升
I didn't think he needed the help.
我認為他不需要幫忙
Well,there's no such thing as enough sales.
銷量的上限是永無止境的
What I did might be wrong,
我做的也許不對
but there's no way I could ever kill anyone.
但我不可能去殺人
Why should I believe you?
我為什麼要相信你呢?
Those letters were a strategic business move.
這些信件不過是商業舉措
I would do anything to help my client sell more books.
為了替客戶售出更多圖書我會不擇手段
Anything.
不擇手段
Well played,boss. You get her in round two?
幹得好 頭 你打算第二輪就讓她招供?
I won't be around to,DiNozzo.
沒有什麼第二輪 DiNozzo
She didn't break.
她沒有崩潰
I know.
我知道
I was there.
我在那兒
She didn't do it,did she?
不是她幹的 對嗎?
She's your publisher.
他是你的出版商
You tell me.
你說呢
I think she's telling the truth.
我認為她吐露的是實情
That makes two of us.
我跟你一樣想法
I compared Crawhaw's DNA to the mystery blood pulled off of Petty Officer Cove.
我把Crawhaw的DNA 和Cove士官那裡找到的神秘血液做了對比
She did not do it.
不是她幹的
I've read this a thousand times and I've come up with nothing.
我已經讀了一千遍了 還是一無所獲
Then maybe we should spitball ideas and see what sticks.
也許應該再多思考下 看哪個站得住腳
What?
什麼?
Did I say it wrong?
我沒說對?
No,you got that right.
不 你說得對
No,that's good.
不 這很好
So start with what we know.
從我們已知的信息入手
Campfire.
營火會開始
Well,we know there's a killer on the loose.
現在我們知道兇手在逃
One down,two to go.
死了一個 還有兩個
And he's already killed number two.
他已經謀殺了第二號角色
In your book,Cameron Meyer and Jared Brenner only have two things in common.
在你的書裡 Cameron Meyer 和Jared Brenner只有兩個共同點
They extorted money and both murdered a convenience store clerk.
搶劫錢財 殺死便利商店店員
Maybe the killer was seeking revenge for the clerk's death.
也許殺手想為死去的店員報仇雪恨
No. The clerk's a throwaway character.
不 店員不過是個一閃而過的角色
I didn't even bother to name him.
我甚至都沒給他起名字
Besides,the stalker letters are fake,
另外 跟蹤狂的信件也是假的
so we don't even know that he's delusional.
所以甚至搞不清楚他是否有在妄想
He murdered two characters from a work of fiction,McGee.
他根據虛構的作品謀殺了兩個角色 McGee
Okay,so he's probably delusional,
好吧 他多半有妄想
but that doesn mean he's looking for revenge.
但並不代表他在伺機報復
You've got to have a motive,probie.
得找出動機 菜鳥
Well,I am not convinced that the answer is in my book,Tony.
我不相信答案在我書裡 Tony
Maybe the answer is in how he got the book.
也許答案在於他怎樣弄到你的書
Heefinitely didn't get it from Crawshaw.
他肯定不是從Crawshaw那裡弄到的
She'd never do anything to jeopardize sales.
她絕不會做出有損銷量的事
It means he got it from you.
也就是說他從你那裡弄到的書
But I keep everything locked up.
可是我把一切都鎖了起來
It wasn't a question.
這不是個問題
It's you or Crawshaw.
不是你就是Crawshaw
Trust your instincts,Tim.
相信你的本能 Tim
They're usually right.
它們通常都是對的
Take the lead on this one.
讓本能來解決這個問題吧
All we can do is assist.
我們只能幫忙
Okay.
好吧
From the beginning...
從頭開始...
page one.
從第一頁開始
I'd say we played that one nicely,boss.
我們表現得不錯 頭
The whole good guy,bad guy technique.
一個唱紅臉 一個唱黑臉
DiNozzo.
Yeah?
什麼事?
Assist.
去幫忙
Hold the elevator!
按住電梯!
I am using muscles I didn't even know I had.
我此刻使用的肌肉 我以前都不知道
No wonder you only got to chapter six.
難怪你只能寫到第六章
Chapter seven.
第七章
It's jazz.
爵士樂
Helps me clear my mind.
幫我理清思路
Coltrane is jazz,McGee.
Coltrane的才算爵士樂 McGee
This is a soundtrack to a bad '70s porno shot in the San Fernando Valley.
這是70年代在聖弗南多谷拍攝的 某個色情電影的原聲音樂
I'm just trying to reenact every detail of my writing process here,okay?
我不過是在重演寫作過程的詳細步驟 行了嗎?
I'm sorry,did you say something?
對不起 你剛說什麼?
My ears are bleeding and I can't...
我的耳朵在流血 我不能...
I..I can't...
我...我不能...
Thank you.
謝謝
I'm trying to show you what I do when I get stuck.
我想讓你知道我寫作陷入僵局時會做什麼
Blocked.
瓶頸
Whatever.
隨你怎麼說
- Up. Come on. - I'm in the middle.
- 起來 快 - 我沒完呢
Up.
起來
Okay.
好吧
Now,sometimes when I'm in trouble,
有時當我感到茫然無措的時候
I take a few minutes to free write.
我就進行幾分鐘自由寫作
Free write?
自由寫作?
Stream of consciousness.
意識流
About my characters,my story arcs, my possible plot lines,
關於角色 故事的方向和可能發生的情節
everything-- no filter.
所有一切 不加過濾
No filter...
不加過濾...
Whatever pops in my head goes right to the page.
腦袋所想直接躍然紙上
Write...
寫
be free.
獲得自由
Just do it.
就這麼做吧
Free write!
自由寫作!
Be free...
為了自由...
I get it.
我明白了
If I like it,I put it in my binder.
如果我喜歡 就把它裝訂到文件夾裡
If not...
如果不喜歡...
You always use your shredder?
你一直使用碎紙機?
Always.
一直如此
You ever just take a stack of pages and toss it in the trash?
你就沒有抓起一堆廢頁扔進垃圾桶?
Never.
從不這樣
You ever misplaced a binder or lost a copy of a book?
你有沒有裝訂錯或遺失過拷貝件呢?
No and no.
不 沒有
The only way the killer got my book is if he broke into my apartment,
兇手要取得我的書稿 唯一的辦法就是破門而入
made a copy and returned the original.
複印後將原稿放回原處
I'm a federal investigator, so I'm sure I would know
我是聯邦調查員
if someone was trying to break into my place.
如果有人想闖到我家裡 我當然能察覺到
We're missing something.
我們漏掉了什麼
While we are trying to figure it out,
我們全力以赴想找出真相時
he is planning on how to kill his next victim.
他正在計劃怎樣殺死下一個受害者
Or he's already killed them.
或者已經殺死他們了
Sorry.
對不起
I was just free thinking.
我這是自由思考
It's like he's here in the room with me looking over my shoulder as I write.
感覺就像我寫的時候 他就在我背後看著
Type.
打字
'Cause technically,what you do is type.
因為從技術上而言 你是在打字
You don't really write.
你沒有真正地書寫
That would be...
這可能...
I type.
我打字
That's how he does it.
他就是這麼做的
Looked over your shoulder?
你從背後看
I type.
我打字
Tony,I type! Tony
Tony 我打字!
Boss,I got it.
頭 我知道了
Film?
膠卷?
It's from my typewriter.
這是從我的打字機上拿下來的
Typewriter ribbons.
打字色帶
It's how the killer read my book.
殺手通過這種方法讀我的小說
Well,where di he get the ribbons?
那他從哪裡取得的色帶?
Trash.
垃圾箱
The killer must have picked them out of McGee's Dumpster.
殺手一定從McGee扔掉的垃圾裡撿的
Means he had access to all my notes and my ideas.
為此 他可以得到我的所有內容和想法
Which means the murders may not be based on just the book.
也就是說兇手不僅僅是按照書本作案
All these pages are a product of my free writing.
這些東西是我自由寫作的產物
Free writing?
自由寫作?
I'll explain it later.
我稍後再作解釋
One of my many possible endings involved
我的多個結局之一就是
Cameron Meyer and Jared Brenner killing me--
Cameron Meyer和Jared Brenner殺死了我
Agent McGregor.
McGregor探員
It's a character I based on myself.
我根據自己塑造出來的角色
If the killer's confusing fiction with reality,
如果兇手將小說與現實混為一談
then you've got a motive.
那你就能找到動機了
He's protecting you.
他在保護你
He's already killed two of the characters-- who's the third?
他已經殺死了兩個角色 第三個是誰?
I haven't decided yet,
我還沒想好
but Meyer and Brenner are the only characters that wanted me-- McGregor-- dead.
但Meyer和Brenner是僅有的兩個 想讓我--McGregor去死的角色
Then why does he think there are three?
那為什麼他認為有三個?
I don't know. I decided it would be stupid to kill McGregor.
不知道 我覺得殺死McGregor太傻了
Everyone likes him too much.
他人見人愛
Well,not everyone.
不是每個人都愛
"Forensic Specialist Amy Sutton offered her heart to Agent McGregor,
"法醫專家Amy Sutton對McGregor一片癡心
only to be rejected.
卻只有被拒絕的命運"
Using sign language, she tells her deaf mother
她用手語告訴失聰的母親
"that she can't live without him.
沒有他她活不下去
He's going to have to go.」
他不得不走
Yeah,"go," as in leave the agency.
是的 "走" 指離開機構
Not "go" as in go.
而不是那種含義的"走"
Does the killer know that?
兇手清楚這點嗎?
Abby?
She's not answering her cell.
她沒接手機
Security detail.
安檢情況
Shift change. They just arrived on duty outside her apartment.
換班 他們剛到她公寓外面
She's gone.
她已經走了
He's not answering her home phone either,Gibbs.
她家裡的電話也沒接 Gibbs
Send them in.
派他們進去
Secure the apartment.
對公寓採取安全措施
No,she's not there.
不 她不在那兒
Her apartment's flooded.
她的公寓大漏水
She's aying with Sister Rosita and the girls.
她跟Rosita修女她們在一起
Sister Rosita?
Rosita修女?
From her bowling team.
跟她一個保齡球隊的
The bowling nuns.
保齡球修女團
Hi,Amy.
嗨 Amy
Still no answer.
還是沒人接
Call again,McGee.
再打 McGee
I can't believe I let this happen.
真不敢相信我會惹出這種事來
Abby kno how to take care of herself,McGee.
Abby知道怎麼照顧自己 McGee
And she's got a crew of nunwatching her back.
還有一群修女在照看著她
Nuns are on a spiritual retreat.
修女在做心靈靜修
She's on her own.
她孤身一人
Are you...
你是...
here to see someone?
來找人的?
because the sisters,they're gone...
因為修女們...都不在...
for a minute.
就一會兒
They went to the church and they should be back any time.
她們去教堂了 隨時都會回來
If you were smart......
如果你放聰明點...
you would've just let him go,Amy.
就應該放他走 Amy
My name is Abby.
我叫Abby
I know rejection is hard.
我知道被人拒絕滋味不好受
But let's face it,
但是面對現實吧
you're not good enough for him anyway.
總之 你配不上他
Good enough for who?
配不上誰?
Special Agent McGregor.
McGregor特別探員
You two take the back.
你們倆走後面
McGee,you're with me.
McGee 你跟我來
I'm sure there's some sort of communication problem here.
肯定我們的交流上有點問題
Don't talk to me like I'm stupid.
別說得我像是個傻瓜一樣
I know what you said.
我知道你說的
That makes one of us.
那就只是我一個人
How were you planning to do it,huh?
你打算怎麼下手?
Do what?
下手做什麼?
Kill him.
殺死他
Was it poison?
下毒?
I bet with your forensic training,
我打賭利用你的法醫培訓
I bet you could come up with something pretty...
你想的辦法會相當...
I wouldn't do that.
我不會這麼做
I will say
我得說
I've always respected your courage,Amy.
我一直欽佩你的勇氣 Amy
Drop your weapon!
放下武器!
He said drop it!
他說放下!
Now!
現在!
Officer Lisa...
Lisa警官...
Agent Tommy.
Tommy探員
I'm afraid I can't do that.
恐怕我辦不到
You don't know it yet,
你們還不知道
but your partner's in danger.
你們的搭檔處境很危險
Landon?
Landon,what are you doing?
Landon 你在幹什麼?
I'm protecting you.
保護你
McGee,who is this guy?
McGee 這傢伙是誰?
He's a friend.
是個朋友
Don't!
別!
I have to do this!
我必須這麼做
Landon,she's not going to hurt me.
Landon 她不會傷害我
It's just a book. It's not...
這不過是本書而沒有...
Finished yet.
完成
Tell him the ending,Agent McGregor.
告訴他結局 McGregor探員
Tell him what happens.
告訴他發生了什麼
It's not what you think.
事情跟你想的不一樣
Landon...
Amy and I...
Amy和我...
Amy and I get married.
Amy和我結婚了
You...
你...
you marry her?
你娶她了?
Yeah,I do.
是的
That means that if you kill her, you're killing the only woman I ever loved.
也就是說 如果你殺害她 就是在殺害我唯一心愛的女人
Landon,I really do love her.
Landon 我真的愛她
It just took me awhile to figure it out.
過了段時間我才弄明白
I was only trying to help.
我不過想幫忙
You killed two people.
你殺了兩個人
I had no choice.
我別無選擇
They set a wedding date yet?
他們定好婚期了嗎?
The guest list is full,buddy.
客人名單滿了 夥計
You okay,Abs?
你還好嗎 Abs?
With the amount of bad guys after me, I feel like I'm dating Spiderman.
那麼多壞人追殺我 感覺我像在跟蝙蝠俠約會
Abby,I'm so sorry.
Abby 對不起
We need to talk.
我們得談談
I know this is all my fault.
我知道都是我的錯
Agent McGregor cannot marry Amy in the end.
McGregor探員最後不可以跟Amy結婚
McGee,they're all wrong for each other.
McGee 他們根本不適合對方